





linkedin.com/in/mohansiva/



An organized and reliable candidate who successfully manages multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on additional responsibilities to achieve team goals.

Experienced employees with experience meeting requirements, improving processes, and exceeding requirements in a team environment. A hardworking individual with excellent communication skills, the ability to prioritize and organize tasks, and a deep understanding of industry concepts.

Work History

NOV 2017- FEB 2018 Customer Service Representative – Part Time Homecenter Lifestyle Pvt Ltd

DEC 2018 - MAR 2019 Finance Trainee - Internship

Ashok leyland Ltd

An internship for the development of accounting and management abilities. The main objective of this intern is to analyse how an organization performs day-to-day operations and to collect three years of journal entries for the purpose of information and studies.

NOV 2019 - FEB 2022 **Data Collection Analyst**

Stats Perform Pvt Ltd

- I worked as a data collection analyst. The work generally is based on statistical information related to sports. Specifically, soccer, basketball, volleyball, and rugby.
- It is my responsibility to analyse and rectify the data. If the information is inaccurate or has replicas in the database, I must update it.
- I set certain limitations and criteria to acquire a decent point of view in a visual presentation so that my peers could comprehend it more easily. And my shift leader loves using this approach while educating new employees.
- Finally, it alters my job speed as a trainer and DCA, and I've moved to different teams to perform what I do effectively.

Skills

- Data collection and review
- Office 365
- Multi-tasking abilities
- HTML & CSS
- Research and data collection
- G-suite
- **Basic Accounting**
- Logo & Illustration Designing

Education

2014

Montfort Matriculation Higher Secondary School Scored: 56.6%

2016

HSC - Commerce Business Mathematics Kumararajah Muthiah Higher Secondary School Scored: 57.42%

2016 - 2019

Bachelor of Commerce – Corporate Secretaryship **Presidency College**

GPA: 3.2

Hobbies & Interests

Mobile gaming is more accessible these days, and I'm usually into gaming, and it's one thing that I'm good at. And I really dug too deep to learn how it all began, so I began my journey to learn how the backend processes are all working, i.e., programmers, graphics engines, programming languages like C, C++, and C#, content creation for mobile gaming, and the final point is creativity, etc. For me, this goes beyond a simple hobby. This hobby has educated me so much. and I'm still figuring things out.